(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T23:10:46.208757",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Whew~ Another hard day's work done...
Huh? Morning already?
And the weather's actually perfect!
Wow!
I'm so exhausted...
And starving.
Honestly, someone should be making me breakfast right now.
Surely there's someone out there willing to take care of me.
Maybe a little walk will help me recharge.
Then I'll invite someone over.
I don't know... Who's around at this hour?
I gotta think about this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oww...
Where am I?
Last thing I remember, I got hit by a car...
Whoa, that's a pretty fancy throne.
Does someone important live here or something?
Ah!
So you're the one who ran me over earlier!
Why were you even driving a car?
Wait...
You can drive?!
With those tiny little arms and legs?
There's no way you could even reach the pedals!
That's why you messed up and ran me over, isn't it?
You know where we are?
How do you not know?!
It's because of you that I'm stuck in some place I don't even recognize!
Finally found you!
Kronii, Warden of Time!
What a long journey it's been... Took forever.
You're not about to tell me you don't even know how to get back home... right?
They're really going at it.
Maybe we should join in too!
If you're saying we should sneak in and attack... sure, but I- I don't want to join.
But we can take them down while they're distracted by fighting.
Fine.
Gigi! CC!
So, one of the Kronies ran me over with a car, and...
when I came to, I was here!
気がついたらここにいたんだけど！
ここがどこだか知ってる？
Do you know where this place is?
なんで私たちのこと知ってるんだろ？
Why does she know who we are?
しかもクロニーズってなんだよ
And what's a "Kronie," anyway?
ここがどこかもわかってないみたいだけど…
She doesn't seem to know where she is, but...
あの人 ここのボスのはずじゃないの？
isn't she supposed to be the boss here?
うん…
Yeah...
それに なんか弱そうだし…
and she kinda looks weak...
うん…
Yeah...
どうしたの…？なに？
What's going on...? What?
やっつけて英雄になるぞ！
Let's beat her and become heroes!
え？！
Huh?!
よし！消えろ クズ！すぐに！
Argh! Die, scum! Die! Now!
いや それはちょっとやりすぎでしょ。
Okay, that's a little too far. Hey...
汚いやつめ！落ち着いて ちょっと 何？
...you filthy, filthy, filthy. Okay, you need to chill out. What?
消えろ 消えろ 消えろー
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her!
冗談でしょ！
Don't kill me!
え？待って なに？なんで攻撃してくるの？
What? Wait, w-why are you even attacking me?
だって ここではあなたがボスなんでしょ？
I mean, you're the boss here, right?
私たちは英雄になるために来たんだ！
We came here to become heroes!
え？あ、勇者ごっこってことね！オッケー！オッケー わかった。
Huh? Ah, so we're playing hero and villain. Okay. Okay, I get you.
ごっこ？これは…これは本物だよ！
Playing? It's... It's real!
オッケー うん いいよ。
Okay. Yeah, sure.
私が勝ったら ご飯作って
Then if I win, I want you two to cook for me
お世話してほしいにゃ〜！
and then take care of me, meow~!
うわわ… いや 遠慮するわ。
Uh-ew... I don't... no thank you.
心配しないで、子猫ちゃん 私がお世話してあげる。
Don't worry, kitten. I'll take care of you.
うん 君のペットになんかなりたくない。
Okay, I don't want to be your pet.
やぁ！
Oh!
ハハハ！
Ha ha ha!
弱いね。いち？！
Loser. One?!
ハハハ！
Ha ha ha!
1ダメージはあった！
There was one damage.
ごっこ遊びにしてもさ。
Even for pretend play.
わかった。なんで君達の攻撃のほうが私のより強いの？
Okay. Why are your attacks stronger than mine?
わぁ ボスにしてはずいぶん弱いね？
Wow, you're pretty weak for a boss, aren't you?
いや 違う 子猫にしては ちょうどいいくらいのダメージを出してるよ。
And, no, she does the right amount of damage for a kitten.
ハハハ！
Ha ha ha!
消えろ！消えろ！
Die! Die!
あぁ わかった もうやめて。
Oh. Okay, you can stop.
ていうか 私って本当にボスなの？
Okay. Um, am I really the boss?
なんで君たちが私の敵なの？私はただ家に帰りたいだけなのに。
Why are you two my enemies? I just want to go home.
うう……あああ……
ddyaahhuuuu uaaaa
なんか急にやばそうだよ！
Something suddenly feels really bad!
私の後ろに隠れて 大張夫 私が受け止める え 何何これ？
Stand behind me. It's okay, I'll tank it. The? What? What is this?
魔法が…急に溢れ出してる！
Magic is suddenly... coming out on its own!
ねえ やめて！そういう意味じゃなくて！
Okay. Don't! Why did you take it that way?
うわぁ！
No, BAD! Argh! No, Oh!
私本当あいつらに勝っちゃった。あぅ！え 今の何だったの？
I actually beat them. Oh! What was that just now?
私って…私って本当にすごいの？めちゃくちゃ強いんだ。
Am I... Am I just really goated? I'm really strong.
でも今なんで勝手に起きたの？
But why did it happen on its own?
勝ったけど……甘やかしてくれる人がもういない。
I won, but now there's nobody left to pamper me.
Unhappy?
悩める人の子よ
If you're dealing with a lotta woes
Unlucky?
人成らざる者も
Then you got to listen very close
Be happy!
弛まず目指せよ
Keep on trying, never give up
生きているんだし
Don't forget that you're alive
目を逸らした過去も
The past you have been running from
退屈な未来も
That boring future yet to come
カウンセリング やれやれ
Still counseling you... Oh my, oh my
古今東西 ピースピース
Universal, peace, peace yeah
Unhappy?
Unlucky?
Be happy!
Undead
Undead, oh
ねえねえ ねえねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey
なんだか どうして
Somehow feeling like there's a fight within
戦っているような そんな気がするの
And it's been going on so long
触れられない 触れたくもない
I don't feel it and don't even wanna try
過去の自分 自分 自分 自分 と
Past version of me, of me, of me, of me
もうとっくに死んでる
And those figures of the old
透明な亡霊と対決
Transparent ghosts over my route
幼気で痛い記憶の奥
The childish and painful memories
残念？
have the deepest roots
もう居ないのに
Nowhere to be seen
あれ？そっちが 良い？アイロニーね
Say what? Way better then? Irony
透かされているのは 現在の自分？
They all see the me of the past
ナンセンス 消えないレッテル
when looking at me now
Yes!
Nonsense, label I can't erase
要は コンプレックス
In essence, a complex
取り憑かれているみたい
It's almost like something's possessing me
巻き付いたまま まだ
It is wrapping tight around
離れない
And won't loosen its bounds
在りし日の自分
The self I used to be before
Undead
Undead, oh
死んじゃいない
Still alive
お前 と お前 の 連鎖
Time is a chain of your own path
生きていることは
To be alive is to always
変わり続けることだ
embrace your inner changes, on and on
不幸に甘んじて
Don't settle for unhappiness
満足するなよ
Don't be complacent in distress
幸せになろうとしないなんて
Not even trying to seize the joy and be happy
卑怯だ
You coward
この世 この世は
Oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
奇怪 奇怪 ファンタジー
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
次は鬼が出るか 蛇が出るか
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
出会って 遭って やっと 始まる物語
With people or monsters and spirits
さあ 人か 化物か
Back on topic
閑話休題 ピースピース
Peace, peace yeah
Past
& future
Can't change the past
Past
& future
Run for the future
カ カ カットイン
Cutting in
なんだか どうして
Somehow feeling like there's nothing to be looking forward to
...feeling inside
There's nothing left to view
Lived long enough, nothing is new
No sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
Saddening?
Too much knowledge results in feeling like
every myth is but another boring evolution
Thrill is what I really want now
Bored and down, used to frown
And this is the way the guidance grew
Rising compliance too, it's like I'm going under a lid
I consumed everything
This one, that one, whichever
And now it all just tastes the same
Undead, oh
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
In any era, your past and your future
are in this very moment
Fulfill the life you're set upon
and truthfully keep moving on
Go for that happy ending
Undead, oh
Still alive, I'm telling this to you now
So never give up on pursuing your happiness
and keep being human
'Cause being numb to suffering
always enduring everything
It's almost as if you're dead, a lot of corpses
Undead, oh
Unhappy? If you're dealing with a lotta woes
Unlucky? Then you gotta listen very close
Be happy! Keep on trying, never give up
Undead, oh, be aware that you're alive
Drowning deep in unhappiness
Or seizing that true happiness
It's on you, on you, it's all on you
Universal, all-embracing all creations
Past and future, can't change the past
Past and future, run for the future
Where people gather and go
You'll find all worries and woes
Oh, you gotta live on through this tale of
Monsters everywhere that you can see
あなた
You
わたし
Me
ふたり
The two of us
ぼっち
All alone
みらい
The future
くらい
Is dark
どこへ
Where
いこーか
Shall we go?
悲しみが壊れて死にそうだ
My sadness is breaking, I feel like dying
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
My cries echo into the starry sky
ああああああああああああ
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
ひろい
The vast
せかい
World
なにを
What
うたおか
Shall we sing?
悲しみがあふれて泣きそうだ
My sadness overflows, I feel like crying
握りしめたその手が冷たくて
The hand I grasped is so cold
ああああああああああああ
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
悲しみが壊れて死にそうだ
My sadness is breaking, I feel like dying
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
My cries echo into the starry sky
悲しみがあふれて泣きそうだ
My sadness overflows, I feel like crying
君の声が彼方に消えていく
Your voice fades away into the distance
ああああああああああああ
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
二人ともアンデッドにしてしまった...
I turned both of them into undead...
うぇーい！
Eyyy!
せっかく友達に会えたと思ったのに
I thought I'd finally been reunited with my friends, too.
こんな暗い場所でひとりぼっちだ
And now I'm all alone in this gloomy place.
ん？これ？
Hm? What's this?
私の名前...HP...
My name... HP...
これ よくあるステータス画面ってやつ？ ああいうの見たことある！
Is this one of those typical status screens? Oh, I've seen these. I've seen these.
待って これ好き よし 見てみよう なんで書いてあるの？
Wait, I love this. Okay, let's see. What's it say?
オッケー クローニー 睡眠とかね うん なるほど納得
Okay, Kronii... Like sleep. Yeah, okay. That makes sense.
え ペットプレイ...？
Oh, pet play...?
何？ いつから私がペットになったの？ そういう趣味はないんだけど
Oh, what? Since when did I become a pet? I'm not even into those.
私が飼い主であるべきでしょ いや そもそもそういう趣味があるわけじゃないけど
I should be the owner. Not that I'm into that to begin with, but...
でも そこが怖いんだよね 誰かの変な妄想が混ざってるみたい 私の考えじゃないからね
but, that's scary. It's like someone's weird fantasy got mixed in here. That's not mine.
あ オッケー あ ストーリー記録用のキーワードまであるんだ
Oh, okay. And there's even a keyword for recording the story.
見ているみんな これを記録して誰かに共有する時は ちゃんとそのキーワードを使ってね
Everyone watching this, make sure to use that keyword when you document it and share it with other people, okay?
えっと それから...そうそうもうひとつ
Well. And, oh yeah. Another thing.
さっきの魔法のこと 指示を出してるの君たちだって分かってるからね
That magic from earlier? I know you guys are the ones giving the commands.
友達に向かってあんな魔法を使わせるようなやつは いったいどんな人だ？！
What kind of person would make me cast something like that at my friends?!
でもあれ本当に強力だったよね？
But it was really powerful, wasn't it?
完全に不意を突かれちゃった
Oh, it completely caught me off guard.
あんな魔法を使えるなら誰にでも勝てるじゃん
Oh. With magic like that, I can beat anybody.
使えたとしても友達には使いたくない そんなの最悪だよ
And even if I could, I wouldn't wanna use it on my friends. That would suck.
あぁ どうやって家に帰ればいいんだろう
Oh. I wonder how I'm supposed to get back home.
私はただ早く誰かにご飯を作ってほしいだけなのに！
I just want to eat someone's cooking already!
あ あとも私も頑張ってるんだから みんな褒めてよね にゃぉ〜
Oh, and I've been trying my best, so I want everyone to praise me, too. Meow!
急に疲れが来てる
I'm crashing out.
あ 私がここのボスってことは... つまりあの玉座に座ってもいいってことだよね？
Oh. If I'm the boss of this place, that means... that means I can sit in that throne, right?
わぁ、すごくかっこいい！待って、めっちゃテンション上がってきた！
Oh, that's so cool. Wait, I'm so excited.
よし じゃあとりあえず椅子に座ってひと休みしよう うん、よし。
Okay. Well, for now, I'm just going to sit in the chair and take a break. Yeah. Okay.
まてよ そこゆく嬢さん 逆子宿らせ
Wait, young lady over there, pregnant with a breech baby
あどけの足らない そんな身体に
With that body that lacks innocence
ただしく回らん 愚図の頭で
With your foolish head that doesn't spin right
天真爛漫！ ほざくな馬鹿め。
Pure and innocent?! Stop barking, you fool.
まちな そこゆく兄さん 何の片割れ？
Wait, young man over there, whose half are you?
ちいさなあの娘の 御花を咲かせ、
Making that little girl's flower bloom,
指きりげんまん 星の彼方へ
A pinky swear to the edge of the stars
陽関三畳！？ くたばれ雑魚め。
An emotional farewell?! Drop dead, you small fry.
「いついつ出やるの？ かごめよかごめ」
"When, oh when will you come out? Kagome, Kagome"
嫌味をからげて 嘲るあなたへ
To you, who wrap insults and sneer
ぴたりと重ねて 吐き出す情け
Perfect alignment, spitting out pity
誰もがやがては 地獄の奥底へ
Eventually, everyone goes to the depths of hell
連れて行かれる
To be dragged away.
あー、触れあって 埋めあって
Ah, touching each other, filling each other up...
勝ち取った幸せを
...the happiness we fought for...
盗られた正義のヒーローが泣いている。
The hero of justice, whose happiness was stolen, is crying.
抱きあって 叩きあって
Hugging each other, hitting each other...
分ちあったあの頃を、
...sharing those days...
忘れてしまえたらどれほど楽だろうか。
How much easier would it be if we could forget it all?
擦り切れた肌かさぶた 傷口が痛む
Scuffed skin, scabs, the wounds hurt
愛しさ交えて 痛む片腹
Mixing in affection, the pain in my side hurts
またまたわがまま ばかなまさか？
Selfishness again? No way, you fool?
まだまだ ながなが まなばなきゃだな！
Still a long, long way to go to learn!
そろそろみんなに 追いつかないと
It's about time I catch up with everyone...
うわごと混じりに 彷徨う回路
Shattered circuits wandering with delirium...
視界を濁ませ はかどる迷子
Clouding my vision, becoming a lost child...
誰もが元から 未来の材料へ あてられている
Everyone is, from the start, destined to be materials for the future.
あー、着飾って 痛がって もぎとった 幸せを
Ah, dressing up, hurting, the happiness I plucked away...
盗られた悲劇の ヒロインが泣いている
The stolen tragic heroine is crying.
わけあって かけあって 重ねあった思い出を
The memories we shared, calculated, and stacked up...
忘れてしまえたら どれほど楽だろうか
How much easier would it be if I could just forget them?
強がったって 嘘はばれるぞ
Even if you act tough, the lie will be exposed.
怖がったって 血は流れるぞ
Even if you're scared, blood will flow.
匿った 傷口開くぞ
The wound you hid will open up.
嫌がったって 傷は痛むぞ
Even if you hate it, the wound will hurt.
じゃれあって 眺めあって 語りあったあのときを
Those times we flirted, gazed, and talked...
思い回しては 悲観に暮れてみる
Thinking back on them, I try to drown in pessimism.
駆け寄って 寄り添って 笑いあったあのときを
Those times we ran close, snuggled, and laughed together...
いっそきれいに 忘れてしまいたいんだ
I'd rather just clean forget them completely.
Welcome to the mind fuck
Mind fuck
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Okay たたちまち独壇場 Listen listen
Okay, total domination, listen listen
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
傾け 振り切ろう
Tilt and shake it off
ヤーーー 唱タイム
Yeah, singing time
天辺の御成り ほらおいで
Heavens descend upon the summit, come on over
宵をコンプリート オーライ
Complete the evening, alright
だんだんノリノリで超簡単
Getting more and more into the groove, super easy
えも言われない ain't nobody stop
Unutterable, ain't nobody stop
全土絢爛豪華 attention 騒ごうか
Splendid and luxurious, attention, shall we make a fuss?
意思表示に もうじき衝撃の声 高らか 堂々登板
A shocking voice will soon be raised to express our intentions, proudly taking the stage
もう伽藍洞は 疾っくの疾う淘汰
The temple cave is already being quickly weeded out
絢爛桜花 御出座しだ
The lavish cherry blossoms have made their appearance
格好つけてる つもりは no no
I'm not trying to look cool, no no
オートマティックに溢れちゃう本能
My instincts overflowing automatically
宣う断頭台の上で 燥げ華麗
Declaring on the guillotine, how splendid and dry
da rat a tat... warning!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気に寿 shout it out, shout it out
Hurray, ready to play, shout it out, shout it out
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
はんなり 感情通りに 八艘飛び shout it out, shout it out
Elegant, jumping from boat to boat according to our emotions, shout it out, shout it out
食らっちゃいな
Feast it all up
rat tat tat tat tat
満開総員 一気に とびきり jump around
In full bloom, all members jump around at once
look at me now 皮膚を破りそうな程に跳ねる心臓
Look at me now, almost breaking the skin, as passionate as a bouncing heart...
くらい激情的な仕様 exotic vox
...to the point of passion. Exotic vox
イニミニマニモ ご来場からのご来光
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, the sun rises from the visitors
かくれんぼしてるその気持ち解放
Release that feeling of playing hide and seek
理性アディオス しゃかりきじみちゃう
Rationality adios, getting all worked up
蛇腹刃 蛇尾 騙る 二枚刃 野心家 嫉妬 するような ジュース
A bellows blade, a snake tail, a deceitful double-edged blade, ambitious juice that makes you jealous
たぶらかすな かっとなっちゃ 嫌 カルマに至る前に 揺蕩うわ
Don't fool me, I don't want to get angry, I'll drift before reaching karma
蛇腹刃 蛇尾 騙る 二枚刃 野心家 嫉妬 するような ジュース
A bellows blade, a snake tail, a deceitful double-edged blade, ambitious juice that makes you jealous
たぶらかすな かっとなっちゃ 嫌 十色のバタフライ
Don't fool me, I don't want to get angry, ten-colored butterfly
no escape
ご存じの通り 騒々しい鼓動に 絆されて もう止まれない
As you know, tied to the noisy heartbeat, I can't stop anymore
衝動に塗装し 描いた daybreak 肺貫通 低音狂
Painted and drawn daybreak on impulse, lung-piercing bass fanatic
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
異例の危険度 比類なき活気充満
Unprecedented danger, filled with unparalleled vitality
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
いちかばちか 嗚呼
All or nothing, ah
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気に寿 shout it out, shout it out
Hurray, ready to play, shout it out, shout it out
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
巻き起こすために stay
To stir things up, stay!
一切合切忘れて shout it out!
Forget everything and shout it out!
右に左まとめて Rat-a-tat-at-at-at
Right, left, bring it all together, rat-a-tat-at-at-at
思いっきり Clap your hands
With all your might, clap your hands
なにはともあれ Shout it out, shout it out!
No matter what, shout it out, shout it out!
駄目 駄目 駄目
No, no, no...
脳みその中から「やめろ馬鹿」と喚くモラリティ
My morals scream from the depths of my brain, "Don't do it, you idiot!"
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darlin' baby darlin'
半端なくラブ！と きらめき浮き足立つフィロソフィ
I love you like crazy! A philosophy that's got me sparkling with anticipation
死ぬほど可愛い上目遣い
The way you look up at me is so adorable it kills me,
なにがし法に触れるくらい
It's almost illegal.
ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽
Scattering madness, I'd squandered it all before I knew it,
この世に生まれた君が悪い
And your existence is to blame.
やたらとしんどい恋煩い
I'm heartsick and it's painful,
バラバラんなる頭とこの身体
My head's severed from my body.
頸動脈からアイラブユーが吹き出て
I love yous spew from my carotid artery,
アイリスアウト
And it's iris out.
一体どうしよう この想いをどうしよう あばらの奥を
What the hell am I supposed to do about these feelings in the back of my ribs?
ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
Sugar crystals melt, ready to ooze into puke.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils dilated to the max, I feel like I'm about to drown to death,
今この世で君だけ大正解
In this world right now you're my one-and-only perfect answer.
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darlin' baby darlin'
ひっくり返っても勝ちようない 君だけルールは適用外
Even if I flip over, belly-up I still couldn't win, the rules don't apply to you.
四つともオセロは黒しかない カツアゲ放題
Opened with four black Othello discs, you dominate.
君が笑顔で放ったアバダケダブラ デコにスティグマ申し訳ねえな
You flung an Avada Kedavra at me with a smile, got a stigma on my forehead, my bad.
矢を刺して 貫いて ここ弱点
Pierce me here with an arrow, right where I'm weakest.
死ぬほど可愛い上目遣い
The way you look up at me is so adorable it kills me,
なにがし法に触れるくらい
It's almost illegal.
ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽
Scattering madness, I'd squandered it all before I knew it,
この世に生まれた君が悪い
And your existence is to blame.
パチモンでもいい 何でもいい 今君と名付いてる全て欲しい
Don't care if it's fake, anything is fine, give me everything with your name on it right now.
頸動脈からアイラブユーが吹き出て
I love yous spew from my carotid artery,
アイリスアウト
And it's iris out.
Iris out!
アイリスアウト
Iris out...
一体どうしよう この想いをどうしよう あばらの奥を
What the hell am I supposed to do about these feelings in the back of my ribs?
ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
Sugar crystals melt, ready to ooze into puke.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils dilated to the max, I feel like I'm about to drown to death,
今この世で君だけ大正解
In this world right now you're my one-and-only perfect answer.
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darlin' baby darlin'
カエラ！
Kaela!
クロニー！やっと知ってる人に会えた！
Kronii! Finally, someone I know!
私もだよ〜！
Yeah, me too!
ここどこなの？
Where even are we?
帰りたいのに帰れないの
I wanna go home but I can't...
私も帰れなくて困ってたんだけど
Well, I've been stuck here too, and couldn't find a way back.
もう帰れないなら楽しむしかないと思うんだよね
But if we can't leave, I figured we might as well enjoy ourselves.
すごく前向きだけど
You know, that's a pretty positive attitude, but...
ここから帰りたくないの？
...don't you wanna go home?
帰りたいよ？
Of course I do.
そういえば
Well, you know, come to think of it...
君はここで何をしてるの？クロニー？
...what are you doing here, Kronii?
なんかここのボスらしくて ここから出られないの
So apparently I'm some kind of boss here, and I can't leave this place.
甘やかしてくれる人もいないし
And there's nobody around to spoil me either.
おや、甘やかしてほしいの？
Oh, you want someone to spoil you?
なら私がよしよししてあげるよ
I can give you some head pats if you like.
ほんと？あなたはそれでいいの？
Really? Y-You're okay with that?
もちろん！おいで！おいで！
Yeah, sure! Come here! Come here!
にゃ〜！にゃ〜！
Meow! Meow!
私もボスだったけど誰も来なくて
I was a boss too, but nobody ever came to see me.
寂しいからこの世界から出たかったんだ
I got lonely, so I wanted to leave this world.
寂しかったからここを離れたかったの？
You wanted to leave because you were lonely?
私はね ジジとセシリアと戦うことになって 何が起きてるのかさっぱり分からなかったのに
I ended up fighting Gigi and CC, and I had no idea what was going on.
まあ 私のところには人が来なくて探検しに来たんだ
Well, nobody came to my place, so I decided to go exploring.
そうだ！私とも戦ってくれる？楽しそう！
Alright! Will you fight me too? It sounds fun!
ちゃんと聞いてないよね...
You aren't really listening, are you...
戦いだって楽しんだもん勝ちだよ！いくよ！
A battle is only fun if you enjoy it! Here I come!
いったいどうしちゃったの？
What's wrong with you?
私の武器はハンマー！いくよ！
So my weapon is a hammer. Here I come!
やぁー！
Hya!
適当にあしらって終わらせようかな
Maybe I'll just humor her and get this over with.
はぁ
Huh...
本気でやらないとおもしろくないよ！
It's no fun if you don't take it seriously!
本気出したらやっつけちゃうでしょ！
But if I do, I'll end up defeating you!
大丈夫大丈夫、ほら来い！
It's fine, it's fine. Come on, hit me with it.
知らないからね
Well, don't say I didn't warn you.
おおー！
Ohoooo!
ほら言ったでしょ
Yeah. See, I told you.
めっちゃやばかった！！！
That was awesome!!
本当にすごいね！
That was amazing!
いや、すごいのはあなただよ！
Oh, you're the amazing one!
いや〜 楽しかった
Well, that was fun.
この世界なんかほっといて
So let's stop worrying about this world,
歌って踊って 楽しい時間を過ごして帰ろう！
sing, dance, and have a good time before we head home!
歌って踊るのはいいけど
I'm fine with the singing and dancing part,
ちょっと突然すぎない？
but isn't this a little sudden?
しかも どうやって帰るつもりなの？
And how exactly are you planning on getting us home?
あぁ...
Well...
わかんない！
I don't know!
順序何それ？愛情何それ？美味しいのって？美味しいのって？
What's order? What's love? Is it tasty? Is it tasty?
ならもう駄目駄目 感情捨て去り いっせーのーで ぶっ飛ぶだけ
Then we're already useless. Cast away emotions, one, two, three, and just fly away!
混沌ブギウギハッピー 特盛り ドン・シャイドン ドン・シャイドン もう
Chaos Boogie Woogie Happy, extra large serving! Don't be shy, don't be shy anymore!
だんだん落ちてくIQ クソワロいっせーのーで死ぬまで踊れ
Our IQ is slowly dropping, so hilarious! One, two, three, let's dance till we die!
完全無欠の病だ
An absolute flawlessness of illness,
補完信なんてあり得ない
complement/completion is impossible.
惨憺たる不安だ の方がいいかな
Miserable anxiety is probably better.
わがままばかりじゃ落ち着かない
Can't settle down with only selfishness,
匂わせがすぎて気持ち悪い
too much hinting is disgusting.
当たり前のことも手に付かない なんて言ったらいい お任せあれ
Can't even do basic things... what should I say? Leave it to me!
世間体とか投げ出したい
I want to throw away social status,
狂ったように泣き出したい
I want to cry out like I'm crazy,
思うがまま生きて消えていきたいな
I want to live as I please and fade away!
順序何それ？愛情何それ？美味しいのって？美味しいのって？
What's order? What's love? Is it tasty? Is it tasty?
ならもう駄目駄目 感情捨て去り いっせーのーで ぶっ飛ぶだけ
Then we're already useless. Cast away emotions, one, two, three, and just fly away!
混沌ブギウギハッピー 特盛り ドン・シャイドン ドン・シャイドン もう
Chaos Boogie Woogie Happy, extra large serving! Don't be shy, don't be shy anymore!
だんだん落ちてく人生 クソワロいっせーのーで死ぬまで踊れ
My life is slowly falling apart, so hilarious! One, two, three, let's dance till we die!
ワン・ツー・スリーで全部放り投げて もういいんだって もういいんだって もう
One, two, three, throw it all away! I don't care anymore, I don't care anymore!
ハッピーをお代わり ギブミーときめき いっせーのーで さあ飛び込め
Another serving of happiness, give me excitement! One, two, three, now dive in!
混沌ブギウギ特盛り もういいんだって もういいんだってもう
Chaos Boogie Woogie extra large serving! I don't care anymore, I don't care anymore!
最低安泰 of my life いっせーのーで ぶっ飛ぶだけ
Worst yet stable my life, one, two, three, and just fly away!
混沌ブギウギハッピー 特盛り ドン・シャイドン ドン・シャイドン もう
Chaos Boogie Woogie Happy, extra large serving! Don't be shy, don't be shy anymore!
だんだん落ちてく人生 クソワロいっせーのーで死ぬまで踊れ
My life is slowly falling apart, so hilarious! One, two, three, let's dance till we die!
もういいや 全部全部ほら 忘れてしまおう
Enough already, look, let's just forget everything!
簡単なことじゃないが 我々ならできるだろうな
It's not easy, but we can probably do it!
Get down
頭でわかっては嘆いた
I understood it in my head, yet I lamented
転がってく様子を嗤った
I mocked the way things rolled along
寂しいとか愛とかわかんない 人間の形は投げだしたんだ
I don't understand loneliness or love, I've thrown away my human form
抱えきれない 言葉だらけの存在証明を
Proof of existence, filled with words I can't hold
この小さな劇場から出らんない
I can't escape from this tiny theater
気づいたら最後逃げ出したい
Once I notice, in the end, I want to run away
僕ら全員演じていたんだ
We were all playing a part
エンドロールに向かってゆくんだ
Heading towards the end credits
さあ皆必死に役を演じて 傍観者なんていないのさ
Now everyone desperately acts their role, there are no bystanders here
「ワタシ」なんてないの どこにだって居ないよ
There's no such thing as "me," I'm not anywhere
ずっと僕は 何者にもなれないで
All this time, I could never become anyone at all
僕ら今 さあさあ 喰らいあって
And now, come on, let us devour each other
延長戦 サレンダーして メーデー
In this overtime, surrender and call out Mayday
淡い愛想 垂れ流し 言の愛憎
Spilling pale amiability, love and hate in words
ドラマチックな展開をどっか期待してんだろう 君も
You're probably expecting a dramatic twist somewhere too, aren't you?
YES YES 息を呑んで
YES YES, holding your breath
采配は そこにあんだ ヘッドショット
The command is right there, headshot!
騒ぐ想いも その心撃ち抜いて
Shoot right through that heart and those racing feelings
さあ まだ見ぬ糸を引いて
Now, pull the unseen strings
黒幕のお出ましさ
The mastermind makes their appearance
その目に映るのは
And what is reflected in those eyes...
触れた
I touched it,
触れたら壊れてしまった
...and it broke when I did.
間違ってく様子を黙った
I silently watched things go wrong.
僕ら全員無垢でありました
We were all innocent back then,
いつの間にやら怪物になったんだ
...and yet before we knew it, we became monsters.
その全てを肯定しないと前に進めないかい
Do we have to accept all of that to move forward?
『まあ君にはきっと無理なんだ』
"Well, it's surely impossible for you."
「だから君にはきっと無理なんだ」
"So it's surely impossible for you."
いつの間にやら外野にいたんだ
Before we knew it, we were on the sidelines,
そんなガヤばかり飛ばしてきたんだ
...hurling nothing but jeers like that.
皆必死に自分を守って
Everyone desperately protects themselves,
救いの手を待ってるのさ
...waiting for a helping hand.
考えたくはないよ
I don't want to think about it.
馬鹿になっていたいも
I'd rather just be a fool.
ずっと僕は何者にもなれないで
I could never become anyone at all...
だから今
So now...
前線上に立って その旗は高く舞って
...stand on the front line, that flag fluttering high.
劣勢 頼る相棒 言葉すら必要ないよ
Outmatched, but with my trusted partner, we don't even need words.
ドラマチックな展開は
A dramatic turn of events...
ドットヒートしてくだろう
...will surely heat up.
君も YES YES 息を呑んで
You too, yes, yes, catch your breath.
再会を誓いあって
Vow to meet again.
ワンチャンスしかない僕の
With my only chance,
一瞬をかけるのさ
I'll bet it all on this instant.
クライマックスみたいな
Like a climax,
手に汗を握るのさ
I'll sweat with anticipation.
ぽつりと鳴いた
I let out a quiet peep.
隠してきた真実はどこにもない
The truth I've hidden is nowhere to be found.
嘲ってきた奴らに居場所はない
There is no place for those who mocked me.
思い出してぽいってして感情はない
Recall it and throw it away, there are no feelings left.
流した涙 理由なんてない
There is no reason for the tears I shed.
優しさに温度も感じられない
I can't even feel warmth in kindness.
差し伸べた手に疑いしかない
There's nothing but suspicion for outstretched hands.
穴が空いて愛は垂れてしまいになったんだ
A hole has opened, and love has drained away.
倒れそうな僕を覗き込んだんだ
You peered in at my collapsing self.
諦めかけた人の前にアンタは
In front of someone who was about to give up,
いつも嘲笑うようにお出ましさ
...you always show up with a sneer.
君にはどんな風に見えてるんだい
How does it look to you?
呼吸を整えてさ
Steady your breathing.
ずっと僕は何者にもなれないで
I could never become anyone at all...
僕ら今
We are now...
さあさあ 喰らいあって
...come on, devouring each other.
延長戦 サレンダーして
In extra time, surrendering...
メーデー 淡い愛想
Mayday, a faint courtesy...
垂れ流し 言の愛憎
...draining away, love and hate of words.
ドラマチックな展開を
A dramatic turn of events...
どうか期待してんだろう
...surely you are expecting it.
君も YES YES 息を呑んで
You too, yes, yes, catch your breath.
采配はそこにあんだ
The leadership is right there.
ヘッドショット 騒ぐ想いも
Headshot, even these clamoring feelings,
その心 撃ち抜いて
shoot right through that heart.
さあ まだ見ぬ糸を引いて
Now, pulling on unseen strings,
黒幕のお出ましさ
...here comes the mastermind.
その目に映るのは
What's reflected in those eyes...
都合の良い思いを燃やして
Burning away these convenient thoughts,
呆れた願いはもう手放した
I've already let go of those ridiculous wishes.
裏切りや秘密が漂って
Betrayal and secrets drift about,
ここから動けない
...and I can't move from here.
生まれてしまった あるいは壊れてしまった
We were born, or perhaps we were broken,
あの日のあの場所でずっと 止まったままでいた未来
...at that place on that day, with our future remaining frozen.
それでも心のどこかで 君を感じていた
Even so, somewhere in my heart, I still felt you.
許せない今の僕は誰
I can't forgive... Who am I now?
ねえ ずっとずっとそばにいたんだ
Hey, I was always, always by your side.
勘違いだって嘘じゃないよ
It's no lie to say it was a misunderstanding.
望んだものじゃなくとも
Even if it's not what we wished for,
あなたに出会えた 痛みだけが
the pain of having met you...
愛だって信じられるように
...is the only thing that allows me to believe in love.
僕に触れないで！ 祈る、セレナーデ
Don't touch me! I pray, a serenade.
僕なしで上手く幸せになってね防ぐ
Go on and find happiness without me.
誰よりもずっと、何を手放しても
More than anyone else, no matter what I let go of,
これが愛だって信じていた、罰をください
I believed this was love, so please punish me.
誰でもない、あなた あなただけ
No one else, only you, always you.
世界がまだ忘れてくれなくても
Even if the world won't forget me yet,
きっと、まだ あなた あなただけ
surely, still only you, always you.
願い疲れても歌うよ セレナーデ（スバル）
Even if I grow tired of wishing, I will sing this serenade.
願い疲れても歌うよ セレナーデ（クロニー）
シナリオ通りのコメディ
A comedy following the scenario,
不幸自慢はハウメニー？
how many are bragging about their misfortune?
エゴイスティックに光った
Shining egoistically,
瞳の中に映ってるあなたは誰？
...who is the "you" reflected in those eyes?
暗闇が光らせた舞台の上で
On the stage lit up by the darkness,
何も知らずにただ踊っていられたならよかった
if only I could have just danced without knowing anything.
希望も不幸も身勝手だ
Both hope and misfortune are selfish,
僕らは 全員共犯者だった
we were all accomplices.
疑う余地もないほど
Beyond any shadow of a doubt,
運命が定まったあの夜から
...ever since that night our fate was sealed,
僕は愛し方を忘れた
...I forgot how to love.
これだけ願って これだけ祈って
Wishing this much, praying this much,
こんな悲しい結末でごめんね
I'm sorry for such a sad ending.
すべて失って すべて消え去っても
Even if I lose everything, and everything vanishes,
ただ君がずっと生きていた痛みが欲しい
I just want the pain that you lived with all along.
あと何回数えたら
How many more times must I count?
あと何回傷つけば
How many more times must I hurt?
あと何回失えば
How many more times must I lose?
あと何回壊れたら
How many more times must I break?
あと何回
How many more times...
あと何回数えたら
if I count...
あと何回
How many more times...
あと何回傷つけば
if I'm hurt...
あと何回失えば
if I lose...
この想いは満たされ
will these feelings be satisfied?
これだけ願って
Having wished so much,
これだけ祈って
praying so much,
こんな悲しい結末でごめんね
I'm sorry for such a sad ending.
すべて失って
Even if I lose everything,
すべてが間違っていても
even if everything is wrong,
僕がずっと愛していた君を
I have always loved you.
消えないで
Don't disappear,
祈るセレナーデ
I pray to the serenade.
僕なしで上手く幸せになってね
Please be happy without me.
誰よりもずっと
More than anyone else, always,
何を手放しても
no matter what I let go of,
これが愛だって信じていた 罰をください
I believed this was love, so please punish me.
誰でもない あなた あなただけ
Nobody else but you, only you.
世界がまだ忘れてくれなくても
Even if the world won't forget me yet,
きっとまだ あなた あなただけ
surely it's still you, only you.
願い疲れても歌うよ セレナーデ
Even if I'm tired of wishing, I'll sing a serenade.
雨が降り去っても
Even if the rain passes,
僕が濡れたって
even if I get drenched,
願い疲れても歌うよ セレナーデ
even if I'm tired of wishing, I'll sing a serenade.
クロニー！
Kronii!
助けに来たよ！
I've come to save you!
やっぱりスバル先輩！
I knew it, Subaru-senpai!
どうして助けが必要ってわかったんですか？
How'd'ya know I needed help?
ずっと見てたからね！
I've been watching the whole time!
ずっと見てたんですか…？
The... the whole time...?
私も？
And me?
見てたよ
I watch you.
ああ そうですか
Oh, okay.
それは怖いですけど なんで？！
That's scary, but... why?!
だったらもっと早く助けてほしかったです！
I... I wish you helped me a lot sooner then!
途中から楽しそうにしてたから
Well, you started having fun halfway through,
どうなるか見守ろうかなと思って！
so I figured I'd see how things played out!
うん
Yeah...
見てた…
I watched...
ただ世界を
just the... world.
オッケー うん
Okay. Yeah.
ああ 世界ね わかりました！
Oh, yeah... The world. Yeah.
まあ確かに楽しかった部分もあったかも
Yeah. I mean, I guess I did end up enjoying parts of it.
でしょ？！
See?!
だから本当に助けが必要なのかなって思ってたんだよ！
That's why I was wondering whether you actually needed saving!
ああ 一応ありがとうございます でも
Aw... well thank you, I guess, but...
本当にここから出るのを手伝ってくれるんですか？
can you really help me get out of here?
あと…
Just...
待って
Please wait.
どこ見てるんですか？
Where are you looking?
あと１曲だけ
Just one more song.
心を込めて歌って踊れば 家に帰れるよ！
If you sing and dance your heart out, you can go home!
本当に？
Really?
やった！
Yay!
世界を見てて！
Just watch the world!
世界！ああ あれが世界なんだ
The world! Oh, so that's the world!
オッケー
Oh, okay.
慢てごめん 見入っちゃってた
Wait. Sorry, I was so fascinated.
スタッフさん
Please staff,
上下上上上上上上
down, up up up up up up.
そうそう！
Yeah, yeah!
本当に？！
Really?!
カエラも戦って歌ったあとに消えたでしょ？
Kaela disappeared after fighting and singing, right?
うん
Yeah.
あれは元の世界に帰ったからなんだよ！
That's because she went back to the original world.
戦って歌ったあとに？
After fighting and singing?
待って それって私も戦わなきゃいけないってことですか？
Wait, does that mean I have to fight too?
うん！
Yep!
そう…
Oh...
わけわかんない！
I don't get it!
なんでそもそも戦わなきゃいけないの？！
Why do we have to fight at all?!
何かの儀式みたいなものだと思って！
Think of it like some kind of ritual!
オッケー じゃあそこに立って攻撃を受けるだけね
Okay, then we just stand there and take the hit,
それで現実世界に戻ったら
and when we get back to the real world,
ご飯を作って私のこと甘やかしてもらうから！！！
you're going to make me food and spoil me!!!
やめろ！お願いやめて！やめて！
Stop! Please stop please stop please.
ちょっと！
YOU!
正気か？！
Are you okay?!
正気なの？！
ノー
No.
ちょっと待って なんでスバルがご飯作るの？！
Wait, why should I cook for you?
それに さっきもう甘やかしてもらってたでしょ！
And besides, you were already getting spoiled earlier!
えー
Eh...
とにかく！
Anyway!
楽しむのが大事！
You should have fun!
喜びこそが鍵なんだよ！！
Joy is the key!
ほんとかなぁ？
You sure about that?
じゃあ楽しませてください
Then you have to entertain me.
にゃー！
Meow!
え？にゃー？
Eh? Meow?
大丈夫…？
Are you okay...?
ノー
No.
とにかく！
Anyway!
スバ友召喚！
I summon Subatomo!
カモン！
Come!
スバ友マジで可愛い！
Subatomo is soooo cute!
マジで可愛いでしょ？ね？
This is "super cute" right?
うん でも
Yeah. But it's...
すごくちっちゃい
...so tiny.
え？ちっちゃい？
Eh? Tiny?
すごく小さい
It's so small.
うん！小さいのが可愛い！
Yeah! Small is cute!
見てるだけで幸せになれるでしょ？
Just looking at it makes you happy, right?
見てるだけで幸せになるでしょ？
はい、まぁ
Yeah, I mean, it's
すごく可愛いけど...
very adorable, but...
私...
I'm...
私もここにいるんですけど
I'm also right here too
にゃ... にゃ〜にゃ〜
Meow... meow meow...
クローニーもマジで可愛い！
Kronii is super cute, too!
でも、でもでも...
But, but this is...
これなに？
What is this?
シャイクローニー？
Shy Kronii?
違います！やめてくださいよ〜！
No, stopppppp!
クローニーはにゃーなの？
Is Kronii a cat?
私、私は...それでいいです
I-it's fine.
わからないなら、もういいです
If you don't know, then, never mind.
うん、もうなんでもいいや
It's... it's whatever.
ちょっと、怖すぎるよクローニー！
That's... way too creepy, Kronii!
ねえ！なんで？！
HEY! What's that mean?!
今日のクローニーはちょっと、ちょっと大丈夫かな？
Today Kronii is a little, little, are you okay?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
私は大丈夫じゃないけど、そんなこと言わないで！
Hey, that's... I'm never okay, but you shouldn't say that!
というか、戦うんですよね？
Anyway, aren't we supposed to fight though?
うん、よし！
Yeah, all right!
スバ友大丈夫？うーん...
Subatomo, are you okay? Hm...
いけ！スバ友！
Go Subatomo!
攻撃！攻撃！行け、行け、行け、行け、攻撃！攻撃！
Attack! Attack! Go go go go go! Attack! Attack!
おまえー！
You!
来い！戻れ、戻れ、戻れ、戻れ、大丈夫？
Come! Back back back back! Are you okay?
なんか...ちょっと弱いかも...ウィークかもこいつ
Subatomo... might be a little underwhelming... This lil guy's a weakling.
さぁ、そろそろ準備しようかな
Well, I guess I should start getting prepared.
全然痛くない、くすぐったくもない。ごめんね
It doesn't even hurt. Not even a tickle. Sorry.
やばいぞ！やばい！
This is bad! Really bad!
スバ友！
Subatomo!
一緒に受けよう！やばい！やばい！やばい！
We're taking this one together! Oh no! Oh no!
もう身代わりだよお前が！
We're taking this one together!
助けて！お願いだよ！お願い！お 願い！
Please, mercy! Please, mercy! Please!
いくよー
Here I go...
わあああ！
Waaah!
そんなのやってないよ...
That's terrible...
イェー！
Yayyy!
ごめんね。でもイェー！！
I'm sorry, but yayyyyy!
スバ友ー！
Subatomo!
大丈夫か、スバ友！
Are you okay, Subatomo?
おお、生きてる。よかった
Oh, it's alive, oh thank god, okay.
大変だった
That was rough.
ほら、楽しんでるでしょ！
See? You're having fun!
たぶんこれで家に帰れるはず！
This should probably get you home now!
頑張って！
Good luck!
イェー！ありがとう！
Yeah! Thank you!
バイ！
Bye.
帰ろう！
Go home!
なんだったんだろう...
What was that...
何が起きているのかよくわからないけど
I don't really get what's going on, but...
どうやら最後にもう1曲歌えば家に帰れるみたい
apparently I can go home if I sing one last song.
じゃあ、やってみよう
So let's do that.
待って、これなに？
Wait. What's this?
なに？うんうん
What? Okay, okay.
上から順番に1つずつ見てみようか
Let's go through them one by one from the top.
何気の役に立つかもしれないし
Maybe they'll be useful for something.
オーロ・クロニー 活動5周年記念...
Ouro Kronii 5th Anniversary...
あぁ、なるほど。これは私の周年を記念したグッズってことだね
Ah, okay. So these are the merch celebrating my anniversary, eh?
さて、何があるんだろうね
Let's see. I wonder what they've got.
どれも結構使えそうだから、一緒に見ていこう
They all seem pretty useful, so let's check it out together.
まずは、バケットハット
First up, we got a bucket hat.
イラストははまなしてんてーに描いてもらいました
The illustration was done by Hama Nashi sensei.
コンセプトは私が...
The concept is me being...
みんなの予想通り！ラスボスです！
you guessed it! The final boss!
リバーシブル仕様でイラストもすごくかっこいい！
It's reversible and the artwork looks really cool!
そして、これをかぶると何となく防御力が上がりそうな気がするかも？
And maybe it would make you feel like it would boost your defense stat?
続いては...
And next up...
ランダム属性アクリルキーホルダー！
we got a random attribute acrylic keychain.
ちびキャラはGurin先生に描いていただきました！
The chibi characters were drawn by Gurin sensei!
どれが出るか楽しみだね！
I wonder which one you'll get, ey, ey?
そしてアクリルキーホルダーの次は、クッションです！
And after the acrylic keychain, we got a cushion!
これもGurin先生に描いてもらいました
The design for this was also done by Gurin sensei.
両面にイラストが入っていて
The cushion has an illustration on both sides,
サイズ感も使いやすいクッションです
and size wise, it's pretty easy to use as well.
次は、可愛いボロスランプです！
Next up, we got this cute Boros Lamp!
明るさを2段階で調整できて
Looks like you can adjust the brightness between two levels,
デザインもすっごく可愛い！
and the design is super duper cute,
暗い場所でも安心だね
and with this, you'll be safe even in dark places.
怖い時もボロスがいてくれるよ、みんな心配しないで
When you're scared he's got you, don't worry everyone.
そして次は、シチュエーションボイスパック！
And coming up next, we got a situation voice pack!
タイトルは「悪役クローニーのラストループ」
The title being "Villainess Kronii's Final Loop."
何だか不穏なタイトルだけど、聴くのが楽しみ！
Sounds pretty ominous, but I can't wait to check it out.
早くチェックしたいな、もう聴いちゃおうかな
I wanna listen to it already.
そして最後に全部購入すると
And finally, if you purchase everything,
everything,
you'll also receive a cheki-style card
with a foil stamped signature,
along with a bonus voice pack.
The card illustration was drawn by...
...you guessed it, Hama Nashi-sensei!
...you guessed it, Hama Nashi sensei!
And as for the bonus voice pack...
it's going to be telling the story of
joining hands
and heading into the final battle in order to bring the loop to an end.
It's going to be very emotional, so go check it out.
Once more, here is the full line up.
Yeah,
every single one of these looks like they'd help me escape this other world,
so I definitely want to get them all.
And with that, looks like that's everything.
So, according to Subaru-senpai,
So, according to Subaru senpai,
all I have to do is sing one more song. So,
whew, here goes. Let me try it.
営みの
The busy life...
街が暮れたら 色めき
...colors the town as night falls.
風たちは運ぶわ
The winds carry away
カラスと人々の群れ
the flock of crows and people.
意味なんか
There is no meaning...
ないさ 暮らしがあるだけ
...to life, we simply live.
ただ腹を空かせて
Just being hungry,
君の元へ帰るんだ
I go back home to you.
物心ついたらふと
As I became old enough to understand,
見上げて思うことが
I looked up and realized...
この世にいる誰も
...that everyone in this world...
二人から
...starts from two people.
胸の中にあるもの
What's deep in my heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will fade away someday,
それは側にいること
it is to be by your side.
いつも思い出して
Never ever forget it.
君の中にあるもの
What you have inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat in the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your...
指の混ざり 頬の香り
...laced fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
みにくいと
The concealed feelings...
秘めた想いは色づき
...considered ugly begin to take on colors,
白鳥は運ぶわ
and swans carry them away,
当たり前を変えながら
changing what is taken for granted.
恋せずにいられないな
I cannot help falling in love,
似た顔も虚構にも
with similar faces and fiction.
愛が生まれるのは
Love is born...
一人から
...from one person.
胸の中にあるもの
What's deep in my heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will fade away someday,
それは側にいること
it is to be by your side.
いつも思い出して
Never ever forget it.
君の中にあるもの
What you have inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat in the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your...
指の混ざり 頬の香り
...laced fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
泣き顔も
Your crying face,
黙る夜も
the night of silence,
揺れる笑顔も
and your wavering smile...
いつまでも
...forever and ever,
forever and ever.
胸の中にあるもの
What's deep in my heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will fade away someday,
それは側にいること
it is to be by your side.
いつも思い出して
Never ever forget it.
君の中にあるもの
What you have inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat in the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your...
指の混ざり 頬の香り
...laced fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
二人を 超えてゆけ
Go beyond two people.
一人を 超えてゆけ
Go beyond one person.
ここはどこ…？
Where am I...?
戻ってきた！
I'm back!
それとも寝てただけ？
...or was I asleep?
全部夢だったの？
Was it all a dream?
わからないな
I dunno.
あぁ 私も歳かな
Oh, I'm getting old.
ほんと変な体験だったな
That was such a weird experience.
あ そうだ！
Oh, yeah.
誰か家に呼ぼうとしてたんだっ！
I was going to invite someone over to my place.
そうそう
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
それで 何か食べるものを作ってもらおうとして…
And then I was going to ask them to make me something to eat.
あ 待って 違う
Oh, wait. No, I'm being-
私まだ偉そうだな
I'm still being arrogant.
お願いじゃなくて命令じゃん
That's not asking. That's giving an order.
まあ 命令して当然だけどね～
Which damn right I should.
いや もっと優しく言わなきゃ
No, I should be nicer about this.
うーん
Um...
ご飯を作って にゃ～
Make me some food, please. Meow~
うん うん そう これが可愛いね
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, that's... That's cute.
こっちのほうがいいね
Yeah, that's more like it. Yeah.
…いや そうでもない みんなどうするつもりなの
Or not. What are they going to do, huh?
あ ごめん 長い1日だったの
Oh, sorry. Been a long day.
ていうか 私は誰に話してるんだろう？
Who am I even talking to?
とにかく…
Anyway...
うん わかんない
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know.
誰を家に呼ぼうかな？
Who should I invite?
こんな時間に誰か来てくれる人いるかな？
Is there going to be someone around at this hour?
よし ちょっと考えよう
I gotta think about this...
あ？！なにこれええーーー！！
Oh, what the fu----
I Reincarnated as a Villainess?! Ouro Kronii 3rd Anniversary LIVE